Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Biology, Honors Theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2008-025
  - Grosenick, Logan Micail, Vicarious and context independent use of transitive inference by an African cichlid fish., 2005 May (Box 6)
  - Grundmann, Nicolas Krasovec, Cardiac Output During Prolonged Exercise: Differences between recent findings and traditional understandings., 6/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Gundersen, Britter, Effects of gadolinium on the ionic currents of squid giant fiber lobe neurons., 2005 May (Box 6)
  - Hammer, Mark, A Novel High-Throughput Enzyme Complementation-Based Assay for G Protein-Coupled Receptor Internalization and Endosomal PI3-Kinase Activity., 2006 June (Box 9)
  - Hanna, John William, Molecular analysis of mannose 6-phosphate receptor recycling., 2001 May (Box 1)
  - Hardin, Lia, Developmental Constraints in Leaf-Stem Allometric Scaling Factors in Phyllodineous Species of the Genus Acacia., 5/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Hassid, Benjamin, Evaluating matrix metalloproteinase expression and oxidative stress in manganese superoxide dismutase transgenic mice following transient focal cerebral ischemia., 2005 May (Box 6)
  - Higgins, Dominique M. O., Generation of Monoclonal Antibody Library against Human Glioblastoma Multiforme Tumor Cells., 2006 May (Box 9)
  - Hollenhorst, Marie, RIT: a new player in T cell anergy?., 2005 February (Box 6)
  - Hong, Deborah W., Attempts to localize human BBS6 and BBS8 in mammalian cell lines yield mixed results., 2005 May (Box 6)
  - Horng, Lily Ming-Sha, BEG4, a novel Shh target gene, causes cytoskeletal projections in C3H10T1/2 cells., 2002 May (Box 1)
  - Hotson, Andrew, Regulation of CFTR and ENaC in H441 small airway epithelial cells., 2002 May (Box 1)
  - Hsu, Andrew R., Effects of lowering core temperature on endurance cycling performance., 2003 May (Box 3)
  - Hu, David, Superior parietal lobule gray matter is disproportionately reduced in individuals with Williams Syndrome., 2002 May (Box 1)
  - Hu, Stephanie w., Deletion analysis of the vertebrate Hedgehog interacting protein (HIP-1): Identification and generation of a soluble Hedgehog-binding domain for investigation of its potential in cancer therapy., 2005 May (Box 6)
  - Huang, Jennifer, The effect of Bordetella pertussis on the expression of major histocompatibility complex class II in human monocytes., 2003 May (Box 3)
  - Huang, Mengfei, Characterizing Niemann-Pick Type C (NPC) protein and the implications of dietary cholesterol in Drosophila melanogaster., 5/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Hui, Jamie, Characterizing the structure and funciton of the human BEG4ßgene., 2003 May (Box 3)
  - Hui, Timothy, Testing the Disinhibition hypothesis of epilepsy through multiple single unit recordings from gerbils., 2006 May (Box 9)
  - Hung, Tiffany, ING4 tumor suppressor function is mediated by H3K4trimethyl recognition via PHD domain., 3/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Huntwork, Sarah, Regulation of CtrA proteolysis and phosphorylation in Caulobacter crescentus., 2003 May (Box 3)
  - Hwa, Jennifer, Characterization of proteins specific to the male germ line in Drosophila., 2002 May (Box 1)
  - Hwang, Calvin, The Circadian System is Necessary for Memory Function in Siberian Hamsters., 5/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Hyman, Sage, An investigation into the feeding ecology of the damselfish Neoglyphidodon melas at Pioneer Bay, Orpheus Island., 2002 September (Box 1)
  - Irani, Afraaz, Thermal stress delivered by a continuous wave CO2 laser results in graded upregulation of Hsp70., 2005 May (Box 6)
  - Jacob, Reza, Transgenic overexpression of brain-derived neurotrophic factor enhances myelination and accelerates axonal development in peripheral nerves of mice., 2003 May (Box 3)
  - Jain, Nick, Knockdown of hZimp10 by lentivirus-delivered shRNA inhibits prostate cancer growth in vitro., 2006 May (Box 9)
  - Johnson, Stephanie, A Molecular Helping Hand: Towards an Understanding of the Force Dependence of Transcription through Roadblocks., 2006 May (Box 9)
  - Ju, Kevin, Trojan Horse Therapy: Tat Mediated Transduction of the BH4 Domain of Bcl-xL Protects against Excitotoxicity., 2006 May (Box 9)
  - Kao, Richard, Humor response in narcoleptic subjects assessed by event-related functional Magnetic Resononance Imaging (efMRI)., 2005 May (Box 6)
  - Karasov, Ariela, Identification and disruption of a rhoptry-localized homologue of sodium hydrogen exchangers in Toxoplasma gondii., 2005 May (Box 6)
  - Kaur, Ravneet, Detection of Free L-Arginine in Precipitated Human Plasma Samples: A Novel Assay for Cardiovascular Disease Risk., 2006 May (Box 9)
  - Kehl, Devin, Video Recording Analysis of Classical Eyeblink Conditioning in Mouse and Characterization of a Cerebellar Response to Eyelid Stimulation., 2006 May (Box 9)
  - Kim, Hanna, A genome-wide screen for methylation-silenced genes in human cancer., 2002 May (Box 1)
  - Kost, Laurie Elizabeth, Determining Nursery Habitat for the Nassau Grouper, Epinephelus striatus, and Spiny Lobster, Panulirus argus, via Laurencia spp. Distribution at Abaco and Andros Islands, Bahamas., 5/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Kung, Stephanie, The Role of PAS, GGDEF, and EAL-domain Containing Proteins in the Physiology of Shewanella oneidensis., 2006 May (Box 9)
  - Laddis, Paul, A role for the Wnt pathway in glioblastoma multiforme., 2005 May (Box 6)
  - Laing, Brian Yoshio, The role of the 26S proteasome in nucleotide excision repair of mammalian cells., 2002 May (Box 2)
  - LaMont, Lauren, Rates of neuroreversion of Sabin oral poliovirus vaccine type III among household contacts of vaccinees in rural Mexico., 2003 May (Box 3)
  - Lau, Catherine Yuan-Hsin, Gene therapy for muscular dystrophies: a novel approach using DNA/RNA oligonucleotides., 2002 May (Box 2)
  - Lee, Dennis Jung-Min, Development of the anti-CD3 single chain Fv molecule (ScFv)., 2003 May (Box 3)
  - Lee, Phoebe H., Elucidating the pancreatic ß-cell insulin secretion pathway in a novel genetic mouse model., 2003 May (Box 3)
  - Lee, Soung-Hun, The role of PALS1 and CRB3 in mammalian cortical development., 5/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Lehnert, Erik, An Improved Microfluidics Device Was Used To Examine the Bleaching of Synechococcus sp. PCC 7942 in Response to Nitrogen Deprivation., 5/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Lehrman, Emily, Elucidating synapse assembly: scaffold protein SYD-2 localizes presynaptic components to the synapse in Caenorhabditis elegans., 2005 May (Box 6)
  - Lemieux, Jacob, Alex Apffel, and Martha Cyert, Chemical Cross-linking and Mass Spectrometry to Identify Protein-Protein Interactions: A Pilot Study on the Yeast 26S Proteasome., 5/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Lerrigo, Robert, Uncovering Novel Hepatoma Up-regulated Protein (HURP) Regulatory Strategies: Aurora A Kinase Controls HURP Microtubule-Binding Activity., 5/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Levy, Jonathan M., Molecular Mechanisms of Axon Pruning in Drosophila Mushroom Bodies., 2006 May (Box 9)
  - Li, Jessica, Human Sulf-2 Silencing: Effects on Breast Cancer Cell Proliferation., 3/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Li, Li, Inorganic Polyphosphate in the Lytic Replications of Phages P1 and fd., 2006 May (Box 9)
  - Li, Victor C., Evolution of the Testis TAFs., 2006 May (Box 9)
  - Liang, Peter Shuang, Subcellular localization and protein expression pattern analysis of mMbtl, a novel member of the Polycomb group family of chromatin remodeling factors., 2003 May (Box 3)
  - Lien, Tony, Exploring Neocortical Dynamics with Calcium Imaging., 5/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Lin, Ken Y., Impaired nitric oxide synthase pathway in diabetes mellitus role of asymmetric dimethylarginine and dimenthylarginine dimethylaminohydrolase., 2003 May (Box 3)
  - Lin, Margaret J., More New cells in the Damaged Substantia Nigra of Adult Rats Pretreated with Nonsteroidal Anti-Inflammatory Drug (NSAID): Implications for Neurogenesis., 2006 May (Box 9)
  - Lin, Sophia, Evaluating the Protective Efficacy of the ER/GR Vector Against Stress-Induced Impairments of Non-Spatial Memory., 5/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Liu, David, Reduced Expression of EZH2 Confers non-MDR1 Taxol Resistance to Ovarian Carcinoma., 5/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Liu, Justin, Molecular and Genetic Markers for Fate Determination and Development of Drosophila Olfactory Neuroblasts., 6/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Liu, Raymond, Modeling HCV-induced B-cell Lymphoproliferative disorders: Identification of cytoskeleton-associated proteins in the CD81 signaling pathway., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Liu, Yisha, The Effects of ADHD on Striatal Volume of Patients with Early-Onset Bipolar Disorder., 5/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Livnat, Adi, Information and the evolution of cooperation., 2001 April (Box 1)
  - Lora, Jessika F., On the Miniaturization of Enzyme Kenetics Assays: Characterizing Colias Eurytheme Phosphoglucomutase., 8/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Luu, Minnelly, Metabolic activation of mitomycin C by the E. coli nitroreductase NfsA., 2003 May (Box 3)
  - Lynch, Margaret, Growth Rates and Population Structure of Black Abalone, Haliotis cracherodii, in the Monterey Bay Region., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - MacPherson, Anna C., Glucocorticoids may play dual role in regulation of CNS inflammation., 5/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Maeda, Lauren S., Partial arrest of T7 RNA polymerase translocation by thymine glycol in the transcribed DNA strand is independent of nucleotide sequence context., 2001 May (Box 1)
  - Maresh, Alison, A study of RhoGAP and RhoGEF genes and their involvement in Drosophila neuronal morphogenesis., 2002 May (Box 2)
  - Margeta, Milica, Transcriptional targets of cyclic nucleotide signaling in the C. elegans sensory nervous system., 5/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Mayne, Elizabeth W., Post-Septational Induction of the SOS DNA Damage Response in Bacillus subtilis., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - McColgan, Bryan, Evolution and sequence variation of HIV-1 subtype C envelope., 2005 May (Box 6)
  - McDonald, Marin Alisa, The role of potassium in ischemia-induced depression of synaptic transmission in hippocampus., 2002 May (Box 2)
  - McLendon, Helen M., A model describing the foraging behavior of the red harvester ant, Pogonomyrmex barbatus., 2005 May (Box 6)
  - Meisel, Joshua Daniel, Efficient knockdown of the human protein DDB2 via RNA interference, and its effect on global genomic repair., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Min, Stuart Y., Carbon Monoxide Production via the Mixed Function Oxidase Pathway., 5/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Mitra, Devarati, A potential approach to study the role of Transcription Coupled Repair in Ultraviolet Sensitive Syndrome., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Morelos, Melissa, Probing ATR function through ATRIP phosphorylation., 2005 May (Box 6)
  - Morganroth, Pamela Anne, A new look at a classic phenomenon: exploring the mechanism of thymineless death in Escherichia coli., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Narasimha, Ajay, The Role of V-src in the Primary Stages of Microvascular Angiogenesis: Alterations in VE-cadherin, b-catenin, and FAK Expression., 5/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Narayana, Sirisha, Autoimmunity in multiple sclerosis: Lipid microarrays identify potential key autoantigen targets in brain inflammation., 2005 May (Box 7)
  - Nava, Raul, Effects of the herbicide atrazine on planula settlement in the Pacific scyphozoan medusa Aurelia labiata., 2005 May (Box 7)
  - Navarro, Rosa, Androgen receptor localization in the Haplochromis burtoni male brain., 2002 May (Box 2)
  - Naylor, Stephen, Mutation in the kinesin superfamily gene kif1B affecting one or more splicing isoforms causes abnormal myelin development in the nervous system of zebrafish., 2005 May (Box 7)
  - Nguyen, Daniel, Using RNA Interference to Investigate if Ubiquitination Regulates Telemerase in Human Fibrosarcoma Cells., 5/1/2007 (Box 13)
  - Nguyen, Khoa, Differential Immune Status in Systemic Juvenile Idiopathic Arthritis (SJIA) during Flare and Quiescence., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Norman, Rachael, Structural and Molecular Interactions of CCR5 with Small Molecule HIV-1 Entry Inhibitors., 5/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Ofstad, Tyler, Beg4, a novel Shh target gene, potentiates Gli transcriptional activity., 5/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Olin, Christopher Everett, Developing Antigen Microarrays for Use in Identifying Systemic Antibody Markers of Neurodegeneration., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Pan, Da, Cutaneous molecular expression profiles in acquired lymphedema: responses to VEGF-C lymphangiogenesis., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Patel, Mithun, Generation of alternating copolymer DNA to examine transcriptional pausing in RNA polymerase., 2002 July (Box 2)
  - Pedatella, Kate, Transplantation of Neural Progenitor Cells and Fibroblasts into Motor Cortex and Striatum of Naive Rats: Survival, Migration, Differentiation, and Functional Outcome., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Percy, Matt, The Role of TGF-beta1 in Functional Recovery Following Cerebral Ischemia., 5/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Pierce, Nathan William, Metalloporphyrin Inhibition of In Vitro Mouse Heme Oxygenase Isozyme Activity and Expression of Bach1., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Pincus, Zachary s., Using gene therapy to remodel the neuronal stress response: disarming the endangering effects of glucocorticoids on hippocampal neurons., 2002 May (Box 2)
  - Pitts, Julie, Refining an FPG assay for oxidative damage to human DNA., 2005 May (Box 7)
  - Prints, Yelena, p^30PUb deletion analysis excludes MBII-52 and determines that Pwcr1/MBII-85 snoRNAs contribute to the Prader-Willi syndrome phenotype., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Pursel, Simone Sigrid Marticke, Identifying and characterizing genes involved in axon pruning and branching in the mushroom body of Drosophila melanogaster., 2001 May (Box 1)
  - Qian, Can (Ting), Characterizing the Role of CD94/NKG2A-Qa1 Interaction in the Cross Talk between Mouse Dendritic Cells and NK Cells., 5/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Quan, Susan, Effect of Hyperbaric Oxygen on the Growth Factor Profile of Normal Fibroblasts., 5/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Raasch, William, The Role of Complex Spikes During Pavlovian Eyeblink Conditioning., 6/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Rahim, Sita Zarina Zainul, The Role of Hemocytes in Drosophila melanogaster Response to Beauveria bassiana Fungal and Serratia marcescens Bacterial Infection., 5/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Ramkumar, Mukund, Overexpression of K+ channels modulates the effects of chronic stress on fear learning., 5/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Rangel, Lara Maria, Behavioral and Preliminary fMRI Examinations Behavioral Contrast Effect in Humans., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Raymond, Amanda, Calibrating the sensitivity of the Golgi two-hybrid assay., 5/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Reddy, Simha, The Evolutionary Consequences of Local Dispersal in Bacterial Populations., 5/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Rodriguez, Edwin Hadalid, Gene Expression Programs of Cellular Hypoxia Response: Heterogeneity and the Role of Hypoxia-Inducible Factor-1alpha (HIF-1alpha)., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Rojansky, Rebecca Bloom, The Role of Yaf9 in Chromatin Remodeling and DNA Repair., 5/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Ross, Jason, Generation of a Monoclonal Antibody Library for the Identification of Ovarian Cancer Stem Cells., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Rumah, Kareem Rashid, Blood-Brain Barrier Breakdwon: A Cause or Consequence of Lesions in Multiple Sclerosis?., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Ryu, Jubin, A global analysis of sex-regulated gene expression in Caenorhabditis elegans., 2001 May (Box 1)
  - Sabnis, Amit J., Developmental Characterization of Dsk4 and Dsk6, Two Mutations Affecting Epidermal Pigmentation in Mice., 5/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Schafer, Robert J., Emergent Behaviors in Foraging Networks of the Red Harvester Ant, Pogonomyrmex barbatus., 5/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Schaffer, Justin, Gene Expression Profiling in Response to Ultraviolet Radiation in Zea Mays Genotypes with Varying UV-B Acclimation., 5/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Schaffer, Paula, Domoic acid in the leopard shark (Triakis semifasciata):absence of neurotoxic effects., 2005 May (Box 7)
  - Schorn, Victor, Determining the Expression Patterns of Histone Methyltransferases in the Developing Mouse Neocortex., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Shah, Naman, Identification of TERT - regulated genes through microarray analysis in vivo., 5/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Sheehan, Jessica M., Estrogen and Progesterone Promote Proliferation and Cell Cycling in Mouse E15 Cortical Slice Cultures., 5/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Shen, John, Determining the Role of Acetylation on the Function of the Retinoblastoma (RB) Tumor Suppressor., 5/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Shin, David S., Boc is an axon guidance receptor involved in the navigation of commissural axons to the ventral midline., 2006 May (Box 10)
  - Sim, Shuzhen, Effect of Nutrient Status on the Formation of Persister Cells in Escherichia coli., 2005 May (Box 7)
  - Singh, Harvir, Development of a Novel Technique to Identify a Tumorigenic Population of Cells from Human Gliomas: The Soft Agar Antibody Array., 2005 May (Box 7)
  - Singh, Maneesh H., Effects of antioxidant and caspase inhibitor gene therapy on mediators of apoptosis in cortical cultures: Investigation of activation, feedback, and crosstalk in apoptotic pathways., 2006 May (Box 11)
  - Stevens, Robin J., Genetic regulation of neural circuits: fruitless and degeneration of Drosophila wing song., 2005 May (Box 7)
  - Sundlass, Karan, Effects of Psychosocial Stress and Running on Neurogenesis., 8/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Tanaka, Tiffany N., Investigating a Role for the Primary Cilium in Dorsal-ventral Patterning of the Mouse Telencephalon., 2006 May (Box 11)
  - Theologic, Alexander Antonios, Adipose-Derived Stromal Cells: Isolation of Pure Populations and their Osteogenic Potential., 5/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Thomas, Molly F., Identification and Characterization of Novel Aurora A and B Substrates During Mitosis and Cytokinesis., 2005 May (Box 7)
  - Thompson, Luke R., Microsatellite analysis of intraspecific genetic variation in four species of Lake Victoria cichlids., 2002 May (Box 2)
  - Tomalty, Katharine M. H., Genetic and Phenotypic Analysis of a Gene Required for Axon Target Selection in Drosophila Visual System., 2006 May (Box 11)
  - Trager, Michelle J., Novel protein mediators of cell division in Caulobacter crescentus., 2001 May (Box 1)
  - Tripp, Eleanor V., Vascular Endothelial Growth Factor-A (VEGF-A) Alternative mRNA Splice Variants and Pulmonary Vascular Remodeling., 5/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Tseng, Diane, Allo-sensitized Donor CD4 Memory T Cells Induce Graft-Versus-Host Disease after Bone Marrow Transplantation., 2006 May (Box 11)
  - Tseng, Yuh Christina, Relation of Submucosal Gland Tissue Volume to Rate of Carbachol Stimulated Mucus Secretion in Lungs from Healthy and Cystic Fibrosis Patients., 5/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Tulloch, Nathaniel, Novel regulation by ExoR and ExoS in Sinorhizobium meliloti: a transcriptional analysis., 5/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Turovskaya, Yana, Characterization of Neuropeptide Y (NPY) Receptor and its Expression Pattern in the African Cichlid Fish, Astatotilapia burtoni., 2006 May (Box 11)
  - Tzvetanov, Ivan T., Stress, Behavior, and Sex Hormones: Using gene therapy to modulate the effects of stress on reference and working memory by blocking the action of stress hormones and mimicking the action of estrogen., 2005 May (Box 7)
  - Umetsu, Sarah E., Human TIM-1 and its Role as an Asthma Susceptibility Gene: Molecular Evidence for the Hygiene Hypothesis., 5/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Venturelli, Ophelia S., The connection between the p53 tumor suppressor and Forkhead transcription factors: implications for longevity and age-related diseases., 5/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Viggiano, Vanessa, The role of Bid in cell-mediated apoptosis of hepatocytes., 2006 May (Box 11)
  - Vyas, Raj, A Study of Drosophila Antennal Lobe Development: Origin of Highly Specific Dendritic/Axonal Innervation Patterns in the Olfactory System., 3/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Walling, Lisa, Nutrient preferences of three families of temperate butterflies: Lycaenidae, Nymphalidae and Pieridae., 2001 May (Box 1)
  - Walsh, Sheila Marie, The role and maintenance of the less common Colias meadii phosphoglucose isomerase genotypes as part of an adaptive response to microclimate variability in the Alpine Zone., 2002 June (Box 2)
  - Wang, Ben, Circularization of VZV genome in SCID mouse model., 2006 May (Box 11)
  - Wang, Jack T., A Genetic Over-expression Screen for Novel Planar Cell Polarity Genes on the X-Chromosome of Drosophila melanogaster., 5/1/2003 (Box 4)
  - Wang, Jing, Characterization of a principal epitope of GAD 65 and Modulation of T cell response by altered peptide ligands., 2002 June (Box 2)
  - Wang, John, Identification and Characterization of Detachment Deficient Mutants in Shewanella oneidensis MR-1., 2006 May (Box 11)
  - Wang, Jordon, Characterization of dBEG4: candidate homologue of human BEG4., 5/1/2003 (Box 5)
  - Wang, Lee, The Influence of Immediate Early 62 Protein Phosphorylation and Cellular Localization on Varicella-Zoster Virus Replication., 5/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Waters, Allison C., Preparation of Living Adult Zebrafish for Brain Imaging., 12/1/2006 (Box 14)
  - Wickramasinghe, Rasika, Molecular dissection of the signaling interactions between sonic hedgehod and FGF pathways in the developing cerebellum., 2002 May (Box 2)
  - Willenberg, Rafer, Biomechanical Comparison of the Prestige II, ProDisc-C, and Spinal Kinetics Artificial Disc Replacements to Anterior Fusion in the Cervical Spine., 2005 May (Box 7)
  - Willis, Danielle A., Isolation and mapping of mutations in the Drosophila melanogaster gene whacked, a gene required for tracheal terminal branch outgrowth., 2002 December (Box 2)
  - Wilson, Ariane, Genotypic and Phenotypic Characterization of Arabidopsis thaliana Mutants Altered in Non-Host Resistance., 5/1/2003 (Box 5)
  - Witten, Daniela M., An analysis of the power of tests of neutrality for DNA polymorphism data to detect selection in the presence of recombination., 2005 May (Box 7)
  - Wong, Kara, The Expression and Role of Laminins in the Development of Melanoma., 2005 May (Box 7)
  - Yang, Ethan Y., b1 Integrin Signaling Blockade Reverses Squamous Cell Carcinoma By Causing Tumor Differentiation and Blocking Invasion., 7/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Yau, Vincent, Sequencing of the ALS2 Gene in a Patient Suspected of Juvenile Onset Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis., 2005 May (Box 7)
  - Ye, Albert S., Inhibition of the signaling kinase KinB by the replication checkpoint protein Sda in Bacillus subtilis., 5/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Yiu, Pannyun, Substrate binding by TRiC chaperonin: insights from retroviral protein p4., 5/1/2003 (Box 5)
  - Yuan, Ye, Characterization of Novel Endothelial Cell Specific Proteins and Their Application to Anti-Angiogenic Therapy., 2006 May (Box 11)
  - Zamora, Cynthia, Evaluation of Oncogene Dependence in MYC-Induced T-cell Lymphomas., 2006 May (Box 11)
  - Zarafshar, Shirin, Does alpha-ketoglutarate participate in regulation of HIF transcription activity?., 2005 May (Box 7)
  - Zaveri, Maulik S., Gelatinase A activity in response to variable blood flow in the arteriovenous fistula model., 3/1/2003 (Box 5)
  - Zhuang, Anne, C-Kit and stem cell factor in the developing murine cerebellum and medulloblastoma., 5/1/2007 (Box 14)
  - Zuzuarregui, Rafael, Increase of Bone Mineral Density in Postmenopausal Women as Influenced by Calcium Intake, Hormone Replacement Therapy and Strength Training Exercise over a Six-Year Period., 2006 May (Box 11)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2008-271
  - Aakre, Christopher D., Analysis of the Bacterial Effector Protein Xopn in the Pathogenesis of Xanthomonas campestris PV. Vesicatoria., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - Abrash, Emily, Defining Regional Identity: the CHALLAH Family Genes and Stomatal Development Networks., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Matthew, Characterization of Dlk Overexpression in Hippocampal Neurons., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - Aow, Jonathan, An Assay to Over-express the Wildtype and Mutants of the Eukaryotic Chaperonin TRiC Using S. cerevisiae., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)